THE SLUT
What do I do, but it's very funny.
The last time I fix your bike.
- Bye.
The end of a rotten egg.
No.
Mother, hide it.
Batla counting.
Thank you.
Mika.
Noa.
Hey.
- How are you?
- I'm fine and you?
I'm fine. I have not seen you for years.
Years.
What are you doing here?
My mom's house...
Yes, I'm so sorry to hear.
Okay, thanks.
Need to pack everything. When you don't know everything.
Still lying here?
Yes.
Even the same at home.
Coop and...
Close to... the girls' school.
- I have two daughters, right?
- Two.
Close to the ground. There is a klinidim.
Very hot.
Rami bicycle shop I'm going.
- Do you remember him?
- I remember.
- Do you need help?
- No, it doesn't matter, thanks.
Are you sure? Not a problem for me.
No, It's too close. Thanks.
Good.
I'm glad Gorutudumusse.
I'm, too.
Bye.
Hey.
New repair etmittim.
Yes, a short period of time.
How are you?
I'm fine, and you?
Good.
What is it?
Tire break, I guess.
How is Noa?
Is it good?
Noa is good.
Leave him here. Take some time.
You get it after the coop.
All right.
Do you have debt?
Okay, goodbye.
What do you need?
Perhaps a good idea.
Pick one.
So, Cartaflar is here. All white.
Beautiful.
Wait a second.
Come here.
Stop it.
Come to me.
Sorry.
Everything's fine, no problem!
Okay, no problem.
Children asleep?
We also want a little bit.
Go back to sleep.
But I want a bit of, Noa wants a little bit.
Not at night, you are fat.
Not fair.
Not fair at all.
Thank you.
Bring it now, okay?
Not so significant.
He mustn't come out, I need to be there.
- We tried.
- Yes.
Hey.
How are you?
Interests in a minute.
Very close.
Sit down.
Girls, this is Shay.
- This is Noa, that is Mika.
- Hello.
- Did you get a sandwich?
- No.
Get it now, okay?
How can a dog?
- Really good.
- Yeah, I mean well.
- Are you okay?
- Good.
- How are you?
- What about you?
- Good.
Good-bye.
- The problem happened, okay?
- Absolutely.
Dönecedim now, okay?
So you leave the henhouse?
No, I just let me out.
Come on, no problem.
Actually, a bit of fresh air walk away. It is good for me to take.
I do not mind.
All right.
Right here let me out.
Thanks.
I came to see if you are hungry.
You something to eat Let's find out.
Actually, I just ate.
Sorry.
No needs to apologize.
Kokutuyorlar this place.
Pick one.
Whichever way?
Get this.
Good choice.
- Who will board the first?
- I.
Put your feet.
Hold tight this place.
- Are you okay?
- Yes.
I want to go faster.
- You want to go faster?
- Yes.
Are you sure?
Are you ready? Pull your hand a little bit.
I am touching here.
Ask Sleeps.
You're so fine Can you stay here?
Till tomorrow. It's a bit sick.
Then I let me see him.
You will see.
Did you see that? Just have to ask.
Or what do you think?
Would be nice.
House refresh.
Actually, it's far from the clinic?
Are not significant.
I'm not interested.
Sorry.
Is a trivial thing.
Is very weak.
Is not no problem.
Thanks.
Thank you.
- Do you need into a renowned else?
- No.
The girls have already uyumutlar sturdy?
I think I do not know. I can not say tey complete.
Good night.
Do you want me to take you tomorrow?
No, the girls in the morning, everything is complicated.
But I already own Batlaryna can go, isn't it?
You said that is Mika.
I am still taking them.
Good night.
Hello, my love.
I'm fine.
Tey should an old house.
Gelecedim there.
Bye.
Wait a second.
Inside of me I want to botalmaný
Are you sure?
Hammers, nails Let's find
Batla!
Let's  Koetk ladies and gentlemen,
on the patio next year
Congratulations on  migrating procces
Now it's my turn.
Do you slept?
Yes.
I am pregnant.
Really?
Are you happy?
Yes.
Yes!
Hey.
- What's new?
- Nothing.
- Not very important.
- No.
A package do you want?
Not so.
No, actually, I thought...
So right now this is a bit fragmented. So...
...Maybe tomorrow?
Yes.
Of course, tomorrow.
Tomorrow.
Okay, so... Bye.
Is this good?
Do you want cheese on?
Then we'll take out of the closet.
Mika take it away.
Can I get a knife, please?
Thanks.
But it's not cheese, I want chocolate.
- What about you?
- I.
So why not you say so? Then you get chocolate.
Quietly.
Go, get your purse.
Do you want to weave my hair?
Come on, let's go.
Okay, goodbye.
Good-bye.
- Welcome, one tey, how are you?
- I'm fine, I need to get a parcel.
Here you go.
- Do you need help?
- No.
Bye.
Hello, my love.
How are you?
I called around, just how are you I wanted to hear.
Of course, no problem.
Good-bye.
Look, I'm just painted.
Do not touch him.
Let's go, can you get a towel?
I'll check.
Yaklat, let me see.
No, it will spread. Do not touch.
Let me see.
Thank you very much. Come here.
Green light, red light!
Here you are.
Bye.
How are you?
Well, I do not feel very good.
Can you girls today I wanted to ask.
No, it's okay, I just...
Yes?
Great.
Thanks.
Bye.
Hey.
- How are you?
- How?
Beautiful.
Let's say that you wanted a Tay.
Girls can take bikes?
- Of course, the coward come.
- All right.
I'll see you then. Thank you,
Good-bye.
Mika - 12.4 seconds. Well done.
- Men want to kotmak?
- Yes.
You got it.
Girls, go play dodgeball.
Guys, come here.
Are you feeling better?
I'm sorry.
I love you.
Hurry!
Want to make an appointment, please.
Here you go.
Yes, for the first time.
Would you like to go back to sleep?
Yes.
Something happened?
I had an abortion.
Sorry.
It's beautiful.
- Can I get a ride?
- No, it is suffering.
Just a little.
Look, Ayad hurt.
But a little bit.
Okay, but it's really a little bit.
Come here.
Is everything all right?
Why not?
What's the problem?
Did you tell your mother?
Why not?
Now you want me to come?
Well, then go find NOA.
Today, the two times I can not.
Find your brother, okay?
Wait for me outside. I'm getting there.
Okay, goodbye.
- Is Churakutiam out?
- No.
How sweet.
Fur, very nice touch.
Eyes, ears, look.
Girls, today you leave your mother.
Clinical have to go.
All right girls?
Why a tey happened?
Something happened. Everything's fine.
Put it back, Mika.
It's locked.
Do not.
Stop it!
You do not like to enter the water?
Not really.
I understand.
How do you feel? Do you want to swim?
No problem, no problem.
Compared to the esoteric.
The phone's ringing.
So look at me.
My mother.
Yes?
It was late at night coming and says.
Tell Olmayacadyny that we have a problem.
No problem, he says.
All right.
Good-bye.
No!
Very Cool!
Stop.
Worm-like arms You need to be.
Mika.
I'll take you to the bed.
I want to watch TV.
Come on, I'll take you to the bed.
Come on.
- Good night, beautiful girl.
- Good night.